[Music]
setting up your local
currency in business Central you can set
up your local currency that is the
currency that you use in the country or
region where you trade
domestically you do this at the general
leder setup I bring up the tell me
search with Al q and I'll search for
general ledger setup notice that I don't
have to type the entire words when I
search I choose General letter set up
from the list and I'll find the lcy code
which is the local currency code it's
set to US dollar so USD which is what I
want in this case I also set the local
currency symol which is what will
display at various places around the
system I also need to describe what the
currency is called in this case US
Dollars now you're set up with your
local
currency now that when you go and create
orders for example it's important that
you don't specify the currency code
unless it's different from your local
currency for example if you trade in a
foreign
currency also make sure that your
currency is not listed among the
currencies in the currencies table let's
just check that I bring up the tell me
search again with lq I go to
currencies select it from the search
result and just check that it does exist
here only the currencies in which I also
trade are listed
here that's how easy it is to set up
your currency your local currency thank
you for
watching